Parunya Tangyoopuwadol

Address: 529/144 Life Bangkok Boulevard Village, Bangwaek Road, Bangwaek, Phasri-charoen, Bangkok 10160

Mobile Phone: +66 855624145 Email: parunya.tang@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Knowledgeable and self-driven Project Specialist with over 2 years of professional experience in financial industry. Demonstrated working with Agile methodology collaboratively with all departments and vendors to successfully deliver technical and non-technical projects within timeline.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2022 - present Business Solutions (Project Specialist), Kasikorn Securities PCL.

- Monitoring and prioritizing projects to deliver valuable projects within timeline
- Maintaining continuously high level of productivity by managing technical and non-technical projects from end to end more than 12 projects quarterly
- Preparing business requirement and test cases to ensure products or services met business needs
- Digitizing services by transforming manual operations into online self-service, resulted in increased of customer satisfaction
- Analyzing business objectives and leading cross-functional team in development and implementation of solutions to meet customers and internal users, resulting in successful project outcomes and improved stakeholder satisfaction
- Negotiating projects cost and timeline with vendors

Key Achievement/Projects

- ➤ KS ONE Mobile Application (iOS & Android) 4.5 stars rating application on App Store with more than a thousand active users in 1 year
- ➤ Bond Trading System New Bond Trading Platform with 1 year project plan
- KS LINE Connect New official LINE with Agent Chat and Personalized Notification features
- > Account Opening via 7-Eleven New channel for opening account

Apr 2021 - Feb 2022 Corporate Strategy, Kasikorn Securities PCL.

- Analyzed the KS online customer journey and present findings to the CEO, resulting in customer journey improvement
- Engaged and collaborated with other departments to improved online services for customers, resulting in increase of customer satisfaction
- Conducted research and analyzed competitors' products and services to strengthen KS business strategy
- Monitored corporate projects to be delivered on time
- Improved communication and engagement with customers and employees

Key Achievement/Projects

- ➤ Global Invest Rebranding Customer journey improvement and rebranding leading to 25% raising in active customers
- > Text detector for leaning account opening process Managed text detector project to reduce approval period from 30 to 5 minutes, resulting in improved operational efficiency and customer experience
- Company Email Improvement Reviewed and revised more than 70 email templates,
- SET Award 2020 (Best Securities)

Parunya Tangyoopuwadol

Address: 529/144 Life Bangkok Boulevard Village, Bangwaek Road, Bangwaek, Phasri-charoen, Bangkok 10160

Mobile Phone: +66 855624145 Email: parunya.tang@gmail.com

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021 Corporate Strategy & Development Analyst (Internship), GetLinks

• Demonstrated strong strategic planning and project management skills by working closely to CEO in managing the project "Human of Tech", the media inspiring people to learn technology, to be delivered on time

Jun 2018 - Jun 2019 Consultant (Intellectual Property - Patent), Tilleke & Gibbins International Company Limited.

- Reviewed and analyzed invention along with legal documents for registering the invention to Thai Patent Office
- Worked closely to clients from multinational companies to respond to Thai Patient Office within tight deadline to prevent applications expiration

May 2017 - July 2017 Yangzhao Exterex Auto Part Industries CO., Ltd., China (internship)

• Observed and achieved in understanding of automotive parts market and manufacturing processes

EDUCATION

Sep 2019 – Sep 2020	Master of Science in Management
	Durham University, United Kingdom (Pass with Merit)
Aug 2014 – May 2018	Bachelor of Engineering in Automotive Design and Manufacturing Engineering
	Chulalongkorn University (GPA 3.04/4.00)

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES & ACHIEVEMENT

Jul 2020 Hack Asia - Gammon Challenge (Virtual Hackathon, Hong Kong)

- Had been selected as 10 finalists to attend 36 hours virtual hackathon competition
- Developed an online market platform as a tool for Gammon to increase their productivity and quality by managing suppliers in the supply chain

Jul 2019 - Sep 2019 Class Representative (Pre-sessional program, Durham University)

• Proven leadership skills by being a class representative to discuss classmates' problems and concerns with University's Student-Staff Consultative Committee

Jan 2019 – Jun 2019 Firm Events Organization Team

- A volunteer who collaboratively work with team to organize internal events e.g. Songkarn Party, Mid-year party
- Demonstrated financial management skills by controlling event's expense within the provided budget

Aug 2017 - Nov 2017 Asian University Alliance Youth Forum (AUAYF)

• The Registration team leader who digitized registration process by using QR code for registration

Aug 2016 - Dec 2016 Budy of Exchange Students (Chulalongkorn University)

That /Niation | Faciliate /Fl

 Volunteered to be a buddy of exchange students which demonstrated the ability of being in an international environment

MISCELLANEOUS

•	Languages	Inal (Native), English (Fluent)
•	Computer Skills	Microsoft Office, Outlook 365
•	Soft Skills	Agile Methodology, Presentation, Working under pressure, Fast Learner
•	Interests	Digital Transformation, Innovation, Gamification, Environment, Traveling, Technology, Yoga